University of Connecticut 1998.0153
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, Vice President for Academic Affairs Office Records [Kenneth Wilson and Anthony DiBenedetto, 1974-1986]
undated, 1962-1983.
1998.0153
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
18.25 Linear feet
The Vice President for Academic Affairs, formerly the Provost, is the chief academic officer of the University and reports directly to the University President. The following University officers report to the Vice President for Academic Affairs: Assistant and Associate Provosts, Deans of Schools and Colleges, and the Directors of the Computer Center, Fiscal Services, Institutional Research, and the University Libraries.
University of Connecticut. Vice President for Academic Affairs Office.
Biography
Kenneth G. Wilson came to the University of Connecticut in 1952 as a Professor of English. He served as Department Head from 1966-1967. In 1967, he was appointed Dean of the College of Liberal Arts and Sciences. In 1970, he was promoted to the position of Vice President for Academic Programs. He became Vice President for Academic Affairs in 1974, a position that replaced that of the Provost. He served in that position until 1981.
Anthony T. DiBenedetto was a Professor of Chemical Engineering at the University of Connecticut from 1972-1980, and served as Department Head from 1972-1977. In 1980, he was named Dean of the Graduate School, and Vice President for Graduate Education and Research. In 1981, he became Vice President for Academic Affairs. DiBenedetto held the position until 1986.
Scope and Content
This collection contains the records of two Vice Presidents for Academic Affairs, Kenneth G. Wilson and Anthony T. DiBenedetto and includes materials dating from 1962 through 1983 [1975-1983, bulk]. The files contain correspondence, reports, publications, legal and financial records related to the ongoing operation of the University.
Arrangement
Series I: Subject Files ( undated, 1971-1983 ) contains general office files, including information on the library, enrichment programs and study abroad.
Series II: President's Office ( 1972-1983 ) includes files on affirmative action, the Institutional Research Office and the UConn Foundation.
Series III: Vice President of Finance and Administration ( 1975-1981 ) contains information on budget, grants and tuition.
Series IV: Vice President for Student Affairs ( undated, 1976-1983 ) contains materials on admissions, minority affairs and student housing.
Series V: Vice President for Graduate Education and Research ( 1980-1981 ) includes information on graduate assistance and the Graduate School Research Foundation.
Series VI: Regional Campuses ( 1974-1983 ) contains information about the University's branch campuses.
Series VII: Schools and Colleges ( 1970-1983 ) contains information on the individual schools and colleges within the University.
Series VIII: Senate ( 1962-1981 ) contains minutes and files from committees such as the Curricula and Courses and Scholastic Standards committees.
Series IX: Centers and Institutes ( 1975-1983 ) includes files on the Center for Academic Programs, the Computer Center, and the Institute of Materials Science.
Series X: Non-University Organizations ( 1978-1983 ) includes files on the American Association of University Professors and National Association of State University and Land Grant Colleges.
Series XI: Outside Agencies ( 1978-1982 ) contains files on the Council of Presidents and the New England Board of Higher Education.
Series XII: Department of Higher Education ( 1981-1983 ) includes information on formula budgeting and admissions standards.
Series XIII: Faculty Summer Fellowships ( 1974-1977 )
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The records were transferred from the Vice President's Office in several accessions.
Return to Provost's Office Records.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Administrative Records.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Notes.; Photocopies.; Press releases.; Publications.; Universities and colleges—United States—Administration.; Universities.; University of Connecticut. Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs.; University of Connecticut—Administration.
- Series I: Subject Files, undated, 1971-1983
  - American Council on Education, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Benton, William Museum of Art, 1981-1982 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Branch Study Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Clark Committee Comments, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 4-5)
  - Council of Presidents, Academic Affairs, 1983 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Health and Safety: Department of Radiation Safety, 1982-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Education, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 8-9)
  - Facilities, Office of, 1981-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 10-11)
  - Grants and Contracts, Office of, 1982-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Degree Study, 1980 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Honors Program, 1980-1981 (Box 1:, Folder 14-15)
  - Human Rights and Opportunities, Council of, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Immigration/Alien Labor, 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Institutional Goals, 1980-1981 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - International Education and Development, Office of, 1981-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 19-23)
  - Library, 1980-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 24-27)
    - Historical Manuscripts and Archives, 1980-1982 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
    - Wilbur Cross space utilization, 1977-1980 (Box 1:, Folder 29-31)
  - New England Association of School and Colleges, 1981-1982 (Box 1:, Folder 32)
  - Personnel Activity Reporting System, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
  - Public Safety Division, Transportation and Traffic Services, 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
  - Personnel, Department of, undated (Box 2:, Folder 35)
    - Advertising, undated (Box 2:, Folder 36)
    - General, undated (Box 2:, Folder 37-38)
    - Organizational Change, 1981-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 39)
    - Organizational Plan, 1982-1983 (Box 2:, Folder 40)
  - Proposals, 1974-1980 (Box 2:, Folder 41-42)
  - Purchasing Department, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 43)
  - Q.P.R. Computation, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 44)
  - Reference: Salary Data, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 45)
  - Registrar, Office of
    - Dual Degree Program, 1980-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 46)
    - General, 1978-1983 (Box 2:, Folder 47-49)
    - Personnel, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 50)
    - Reorganization of Office, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 51)
    - Scheduling Office, 1971-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 52-53)
    - Examinations, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 54)
    - Software System, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 55)
  - Russel, Maria: project, undated (Box 2:, Folder 56)
  - Special Academic and Enrichment Programs
    - Advisory Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 58)
    - Reports on Minorities and Human Rights, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 59)
    - Status Reports and Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 2:, Folder 60)
    - Student Data, 1980-1981 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
  - Study Abroad
    - Armenian Studies Proposal, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 62)
    - Belgrade Exchange Program, 1975-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 63)
    - Center for Slavic and East European Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
    - Chiva Program, 1978-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 65)
    - Cordoba Consortium, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 66)
    - Foundation for International Cooperation, 1978 (Box 2:, Folder 67)
    - France, undated (Box 2:, Folder 68)
    - General, 1978-1983 (Box 2:, Folder 69-71)
    - Hungary Group Project, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 72)
    - International Exchange Program, 1980-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 73)
    - International Studies Program, 1978-1981 (Box 2:, Folder 74)
    - Israel, Center for Study, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 75)
      - Haifa University, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 76)
      - Wingate Institute, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 77)
    - Jagellonian University, Krakow, Poland, 1976-1983 (Box 2:, Folder 78)
    - Latin American Studies, 1978-1981 (Box 2:, Folder 79)
    - Mexico Program, 1979 (Box 2:, Folder 80)
    - Middle East / Islamic Studies, 1978-1981 (Box 2:, Folder 81)
    - Paraiba University, Brazil, 1979-1983 (Box 3:, Folder 82)
    - Portugal Program, 1979 (Box 3:, Folder 83)
    - Puerto Rico University Exchange, 1978 (Box 3:, Folder 84)
    - Pushkin Institute, Russia, 1978 (Box 3:, Folder 85)
    - Warsaw Technical University, 1982-1983 (Box 3:, Folder 86)
    - Wiesbaden Exchange Program, 1980 (Box 3:, Folder 87)
    - Zagazig University, Egypt, 1977-1983 (Box 3:, Folder 88-90)
  - Tucker-Alderfer Report, 1980 (Box 3:, Folder 91)
  - Tuition/fees, 1981-1982 (Box 3:, Folder 92)
  - Undergraduate Laboratories, 1983 (Box 3:, Folder 93)
  - University Computer Systems, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 3:, Folder 94-95)
  - Upper Division Status, 1980 (Box 3:, Folder 96)
  - Women's Studies Program, 1982 (Box 3:, Folder 97)
- Series II: President's Office, 1972-1983
  - Affirmative Action
    - Advisory Committee (BHE), 1979-1980 (Box 4:, Folder 98)
    - Cabinet Consideration of A.A. Policy, 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 99-100)
    - Committee for Goals Implementation, 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 101)
      - Employee Distribution, 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 102)
      - Goals and Timetables, 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 103)
      - Utilization and Searches, 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 104)
    - Plan, 1979 (Box 4:, Folder 105)
  - Affirmative Action Programs, Office for, 1979-1983 (Box 4:, Folder 106-108)
  - Affirmative Action Reports, 1975-1981 (Box 4:, Folder 109)
  - Affirmative Action Scholarship Audit, 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 110)
  - Alumni Association, 1978-1982 (Box 4:, Folder 111)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 4:, Folder 112)
  - Development Office, 1979-1983 (Box 4:, Folder 113-116)
  - General Counsel, Office of the, 1972-1979 (Box 4:, Folder 117-118)
  - Government Relations: Assistant to the President ( Krisst, Ilse), 1981 (Box 4:, Folder 119)
  - Institutional Research, Office of
    - B.H.E. related, 1980 (Box 4:, Folder 120)
    - D.H.E. related, 1981 (Box 4:, Folder 121)
    - Enrollment, 1981-1982 (Box 4:, Folder 122-123)
    - Fact Book, 1981-1982 (Box 4:, Folder 124)
    - Faculty Data, 1980-1982 (Box 4:, Folder 125-126)
    - Student Evaluations, 1981-1983 (Box 4:, Folder 127)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 4:, Folder 128)
    - General Data, 1980-1983 (Box 5:, Folder 129-130)
    - HEGIS, 1980 (Box 5:, Folder 131)
    - Questionnaire (AUDC), 1980 (Box 5:, Folder 132)
    - Salary Data, 1980-1981 (Box 5:, Folder 133-137)
    - Student Data, 1982-1983 (Box 6:, Folder 138)
  - Legislation, 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 139)
  - Ombudsman, Office of the, 1979 (Box 6:, Folder 140)
  - President, Office of the, 1974-1981 (Box 6:, Folder 141)
  - Public Information, Office of, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 142)
  - University of Connecticut Foundation
    - General, 1978-1982 (Box 6:, Folder 143-144)
    - Mears Agreement, undated (Box 6:, Folder 145)
    - Pfizer/Miller Agreement, undated (Box 6:, Folder 146)
  - University Publications, 1979 (Box 6:, Folder 147)
- Series III: Vice President of Finance and Administration, 1975-1981
  - Athletics, Division of, 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 148)
  - Auditorium (Jorgensen), 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 149)
  - Budget
    - Flexibility Issues, 1979-1980 (Box 7:, Folder 150)
    - Development Office, 1980-1981 (Box 7:, Folder 151)
    - Overview, 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 152)
  - Computer Systems, 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 153)
  - Controller, Office of the, 1980-1981 (Box 7:, Folder 154)
    - Payroll Department, 1976-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 155)
  - Environmental Health and Safety: Occupational Health and Safety, Department of, 1975-1978 (Box 7:, Folder 156)
  - Facilities: Transition Plan, 1981 (Box 7:, Folder 157)
  - Financial Aid, 1979-1981 (Box 7:, Folder 158)
  - Grants and Contracts, Office of, 1980-1981 (Box 7:, Folder 159-162)
  - Housing Extensions, 1981 (Box 8:, Folder 163)
  - Liability of UConn Administration, 1981 (Box 8:, Folder 164)
  - Personnel Activity Reporting System, 1981 (Box 8:, Folder 165-167)
  - Physical Plant, 1980-1981 (Box 8:, Folder 168)
  - Public Safety Division, 1975-1981 (Box 8:, Folder 169)
  - Purchasing Department, 1981 (Box 8:, Folder 170)
  - Real Properties and Telecommunications Office, 1980-1981 (Box 8:, Folder 171)
  - Tuition Income, 1981 (Box 8:, Folder 172)
  - Tuition Wavers, 1977-1981 (Box 8:, Folder 173)
- Series IV: Vice President for Student Affairs, undated, 1976-1983
  - Activities Office, 1981 (Box 9:, Folder 174)
  - Admissions, 1980-1981 (Box 9:, Folder 175)
  - Admissions and Orientation Services, 1982-1983 (Box 9:, Folder 176-177)
  - Admission Reports, 1981 (Box 9:, Folder 178)
  - Confidentiality of Student Data, 1976 (Box 9:, Folder 179)
  - Dean's File, 1977-1980 (Box 9:, Folder 180)
  - General, 1980-1983 (Box 9:, Folder 181-182)
  - International Education and Development Office, 1982 (Box 9:, Folder 183)
  - Minority Affairs, undated (Box 9:, Folder 184)
  - Placement and Career Planning Office, 1979-1981 (Box 9:, Folder 185)
  - Residential Life Office, 1980-1982 (Box 9:, Folder 186)
  - Student Housing, 1981-1982 (Box 9:, Folder 187)
  - Transfers, 1977-1979 (Box 9:, Folder 188)
  - WHUS, 1977-1982 (Box 9:, Folder 189)
- Series V: Vice President for Graduate Education and Research, 1980-1981
  - Capita Investment in Research, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 190)
  - General, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 191)
  - Graduate Assistants, 1981 (Box 10:, Folder 192)
  - Graduate School, 1980-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 193-196)
- Series VI: Regional Campuses, 1974-1983
  - Avery Point, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
    - Branford House, 1980-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 197-200)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 201)
    - Project Oceanology, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 202)
  - Branch Enrollment, 1980-1981 (Box 11:, Folder 203)
  - Hartford, 1980-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 204-207)
  - Regional Campuses, 1974-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 208-211)
  - Space Utilization, 1978-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 212-214)
  - Stamford, 1980-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 215-217)
  - Torrington, 1979-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 218-224)
  - Torrington, 1981-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 225-226)
  - Waterbury, 1980-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 227-236)
- Series VII: Schools and Colleges, 1970-1983
  - College of Agriculture and Natural Resources
    - Agriculture Economics and Rural Sociology, Department of, 1979-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 237)
    - Agriculture Engineering, Department of, 1979-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 238)
    - Agriculture Experiment Station, 1980-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 239-240)
    - Animal Genetics, 1977-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 241)
    - Animal Industries, 1979-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 242-244)
    - Animal Inventory, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 245)
    - Bankhead-Hones Monies, 1979-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 246)
    - Cooperative Extension Service, 1979-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 247)
    - General, 1980-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 248-249)
    - Nutritional Sciences, 1979-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 250)
    - Pathobiology, 1979-1980 (Box 13:, Folder 251)
    - Plant Science, 1972-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 252)
    - Renewable Natural Resources, 1979-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 253)
  - School of Allied Health Professionals
    - Allied Health/Nursing Relocation, 1982-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 254-255)
    - General, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 256)
  - School of Business Administration
    - Accounting, 1979-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 257-258)
    - Business Environment and Policy, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 259)
    - Dean, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 260)
    - Harvey Report, 1971-1973 (Box 13:, Folder 261-262)
    - Doctoral Program Proposal, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 263-264)
    - Finance Department, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 265-266)
    - General, 1980-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 267-270)
    - Information Management, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 271)
    - Management and Human Resources Development, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 272)
    - Management and Administration Science, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 273)
    - Marketing, 1980-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 274-275)
    - M.B.A. Program, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 276)
    - M.B.A. Policy Manual, 1978-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 277)
  - College of Liberal Arts and Sciences
    - Anthropology, 1981-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 278-279)
    - Bachelor of General Studies Program, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 280)
    - Biobehavioral Sciences
      - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 281)
      - General, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 282-283)
      - General, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 284)
      - Electron Microscopy lab, 1979-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 285)
      - General, 1978-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 286-288)
      - Museum of Natural History, 1981-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 289)
      - Personnel, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 290-291)
      - Physical Plant, 1982-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 292-299)
    - Chemistry, 1981-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 300)
    - Communications Services, 1980-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 301)
    - Dean, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 302)
    - Economics, 1981-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 303-304)
    - English, 1982-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 305-310)
    - Foreign Languages, 1981-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 311)
    - General, 1981-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 312-313)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 1981-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 314-316)
    - High School Cooperative Program, 1980-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 317-318)
    - History, 1981-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 319-320)
    - Linguistics, 1976 (Box 14:, Folder 321)
    - Mathematics, 1970-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 322-323)
    - Philosophy, 1977-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 324-325)
    - Physics, 1978-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 326-327)
    - Political Science, 1978-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 328-329)
    - Psychology, 1981-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 330-331)
    - R.O.T.C., 1981-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 332-333)
    - Sociology, 1974-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 334-335)
    - Statistics, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 336)
    - Student Internships, 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 337)
    - Women's Studies Program, 1979-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 338)
  - Dental Medicine, School of, 1978-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 339)
  - Education, School of
    - Cooperative Programs: Yale and UConn, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 340)
    - Curriculum and Instruction, 1979-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 341-342)
    - Dean Review, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 343)
    - Education Psychology, 1982-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 344-345)
    - Educational Studies and Instructional Media Program, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 346)
    - Foundations and Curriculum, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 347)
    - General, 1981-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 348-349)
    - Higher Technical and Adult Education, 1978-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 350)
    - Higher Technical and Adult Education, 1978-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 351)
    - E.O. Smith High School, 1978-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 352-355)
    - Sport and Leisure Issue Studies, 1981-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 356-359)
    - Instruction Media, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 360)
  - Engineering, School of
    - Bachelor of Technology, 1974-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 361)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1981-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 362-363)
    - Civil Engineering, 1980-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 364-365)
    - Dean's Office, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 366-367)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1979-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 368-369)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 370-371)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1980-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 372)
    - Metallurgy, 1980-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 373)
  - Extended and Continuing Education, Division of
    - Conferences and Institutes, 1983 (Box 15:, Folder 374)
    - Credit Programs, 1982 (Box 15:, Folder 375)
    - Dean's Office, 1987-1989 (Box 15:, Folder 376)
    - Deanship Review, 1980 (Box 15:, Folder 377)
    - General, 1980-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 378)
    - Non-credit Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 379-380)
  - Family Studies, School of
    - Child Development Laboratories, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 381)
    - General, 1979-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 382-383)
    - Gerontology Program and Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 384)
    - Gerontology, University Program of, 1982 (Box 15:, Folder 385)
    - Interior Design Program, 1982 (Box 15:, Folder 386)
    - Name Change, 1982 (Box 15:, Folder 387)
  - Fine Arts, School of
    - Accreditation, 1982 (Box 15:, Folder 388)
    - Art, 1981-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 389-390)
    - Dramatic Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 391)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 392)
    - Correspondence and Brochures, 1980-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 393-394)
    - Music, 1980-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 395-396)
  - Graduate School
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 397-398)
    - International Student Office, 1980-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 399)
    - Masters of Public Affairs Program, 1981-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 400)
    - Neurosciences Program, 1981-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 401)
    - Ph.D. Program Evaluations, 1982 (Box 15:, Folder 402)
    - Radiation Safety, 1980 (Box 15:, Folder 403)
    - Research Foundation, 1981-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 404)
    - Sea Grant, 1982 (Box 16:, Folder 405-407)
  - Health Center
    - Center for International Community Health Studies Grant Proposal, 1981 (Box 16:, Folder 408)
    - Cluster Program, 1981-1982 (Box 16:, Folder 409-410)
    - General, 1980-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 411)
  - Law School
    - Accreditation, 1983 (Box 16:, Folder 412)
    - Budget/Funding, 1982 (Box 16:, Folder 413)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 414-416)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 417-418)
    - Library, 1983 (Box 16:, Folder 419)
    - Personnel Issues, 1982 (Box 16:, Folder 420)
    - Renovations Project, Phase II, 1982-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 421)
  - Medicine, School of
    - General, 1980-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 422)
  - Nursing, School of
    - General, 1973-1980 (Box 16:, Folder 423-424)
  - Pharmacy, School of
    - General, 1980-1982 (Box 16:, Folder 425)
    - N.M.R. Spectroscopy, 1983 (Box 16:, Folder 426)
  - Ratcliff Hicks School of Agriculture
    - General, 1973-1980 (Box 16:, Folder 427)
  - Social Work, School of
    - Accreditation, 1982 (Box 16:, Folder 428)
    - Budget/Funding, 1982-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 429)
    - Deanship Search ( Robert Green), 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 430)
    - Financial Aid, 1982 (Box 16:, Folder 431)
    - General, 1981-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 432-435)
    - Personnel Issues, 1982 (Box 16:, Folder 436-437)
    - Title XX Training Program, 1980-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 438)
  - Veterinary Medicine
    - General, 1978-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 439-440)
- Series VIII: Senate, 1962-1981
  - Budget Committee, 1981 (Box 17:, Folder 441)
  - Commencement/Convocation, 1976-1980 (Box 17:, Folder 442)
  - Curricula and Courses Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 17:, Folder 443-445)
  - Faculty Standards Committee, 1967-1980 (Box 17:, Folder 446-451)
  - Growth and Development Committee, 1968-1974 (Box 17:, Folder 452)
  - Senate Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 17:, Folder 453)
  - Nominating Committee, 1962-1975 (Box 17:, Folder 454-455)
  - Scholastic Standards Committee, 1970-1981 (Box 17:, Folder 456-461)
- Series IX: Centers and Institutes, 1975-1983
  - Academic Programs, Center for
    - Academic Coordinator for Athletics, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 462)
    - Budgets for Programs, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 463)
    - Connecticut Pre-collegiate Enrichment Program, 1982-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 464-465)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 466-467)
    - Learning Disability Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 18:, Folder 468)
    - Minority Students, Committee for the Education of, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 469)
    - Personnel: correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 470)
    - Purpose Statements, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 471)
    - SAEP/CAP Transition, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 472)
    - Student Issues, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 473)
    - Student Retention, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 474)